Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Phoenix's Homecoming=
=عودة فينيكس إلى الوطن=
=Episode 14=
=الحلقة 14=
(It's Huaiyong's handwriting.)
(هذا خط يد هوايونغ.)
(How have you been?)
(كيف كان حالك؟)
Has anyone bullied you?
هل تعرضت للتنمر من قبل أحد؟
Everything is fine.
كل شيء على ما يرام.
No one dares to bully me.
لا أحد يجرؤ على التنمر عليّ.
You can tell me anything.
يمكنك أن تخبرني بأي شيء.
I've made
لقد صنعت
significant progress with the investigation.
تم إحراز تقدم كبير في التحقيق.
I'll return
سأعود
to see you soon.
أراك قريباً.
I was out on business today
كنتُ خارج المنزل في مهمة عمل اليوم
and came across a temple fair in the mountains.
ووجدوا أنفسهم أمام سوق معبد في الجبال.
People were making wishes there.
كان الناس يتمنون الأمنيات هناك.
You present yourself as my fiancée.
تقدمين نفسكِ على أنكِ خطيبتي.
How I wish all this were real.
أتمنى لو كان كل هذا حقيقياً.
I wrote you a prayer charm.
لقد كتبت لك تعويذة دعاء.
May you have peace and good health.
أتمنى لكم السلام والصحة الجيدة.
I had time to kill,
كان لدي وقت فراغ،
so I needed something to do.
لذلك كنت بحاجة إلى شيء أفعله.
Your hairpin
دبوس شعرك
is almost ready.
يكاد يكون جاهزاً.
I remember that you loved
أتذكر أنك كنت تحب
crabapple blossoms at the academy.
أزهار التفاح البري في الأكاديمية.
You used to mock our classmate Chu
كنت تسخر من زميلنا تشو
that he was eager
أنه كان متلهفاً
to go home every day.
أن أعود إلى المنزل كل يوم.
Now I truly understand how he felt.
الآن أفهم تماماً ما كان يشعر به.
Remember.
يتذكر.
Take good care of yourself.
اعتني بنفسك جيداً.
I'm always
أنا دائماً
thinking of you.
أفكر فيك.
So this is how it feels
هذا هو الشعور إذن
to have someone care about me.
أن يكون هناك من يهتم لأمري.
(To Huaiyong.)
(إلى هواييونغ.)
(I hope you are well.)
(أتمنى أن تكون جيد.)
(I came to the palace)
(أتيت إلى القصر)
(because an old piece of pawn may prove crucial)
(لأن قطعة رهان قديمة قد تثبت أهميتها)
(at a critical moment.)
(في لحظة حرجة.)
(The Sheng army's name wasn't cleared.)
(لم يتم توضيح اسم جيش شينغ.)
(I won't act recklessly.)
(لن أتصرف بتهور.)
(Once you return,)
(عند عودتك،)
(we'll devise a plan.)
(سنضع خطة.)
(Don't worry.)
(لا تقلق.)
The guards are changed at midnight.
يتم تغيير الحراس عند منتصف الليل.
You're on duty, Commander Wei.
أنت في الخدمة، أيها القائد وي.
Why would you have time to wander around Yeyou Court?
لماذا سيكون لديك وقت للتجول في قصر يييو؟
Are you meeting someone?
هل ستلتقي بشخص ما؟
Who are you really?
من أنت حقاً؟
Commander, do you recognize this tiger tally?
أيها القائد، هل تتعرف على هذا العدد من النمور؟
No way.
مستحيل.
But you clearly...
لكن من الواضح أنك...
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
the wronged souls of the Weiyang Palace and the Sheng army
أرواح قصر وييانغ المظلومة وجيش شينغ
dragged me back from the underworld.
سحبني من العالم السفلي.
Years ago, I placed a pawn in the palace.
قبل سنوات، وضعت بيدقاً في القصر.
This pawn was never activated.
لم يتم تفعيل هذا البيدق مطلقا.
The day has come.
لقد حان اليوم.
I've also
لقد فعلتُ أيضاً
been waiting for this day.
كنت أنتظر هذا اليوم.
I, Commander Sheng Weiling of the Sheng army,
أنا، القائد شينغ ويلينغ من جيش شينغ،
pay my respects to Your Highness.
أبلغ سموكم احترامي.
(Sheng)
(شينغ)
Commander Wei.
القائد وي.
I wonder if that fire years ago
أتساءل عما إذا كان ذلك الحريق قد حدث قبل سنوات
had burned away your loyalty.
لقد أحرقت ولاءك.
I should have died
كان ينبغي أن أموت
when the Sheng army was annihilated.
عندما تم إبادة جيش شينغ.
I've clung to life
لقد تشبثت بالحياة
only to clear
فقط للتوضيح
the Sheng army's name one day.
اسم جيش شينغ يوماً ما.
The tally is complete.
اكتملت عملية الإحصاء.
I swear to protect Your Highness with my life.
أقسم أن أحمي سموكم بروحي.
Despite all hardships,
رغم كل الصعاب،
I will never retreat.
لن أتراجع أبداً.
It's the incense my sister used.
إنه البخور الذي كانت تستخدمه أختي.
You did serve at the Weiyang Palace.
لقد خدمت في قصر وييانغ.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
No water's enough after seeing the sea.
لا يكفي الماء بعد رؤية البحر.
No clouds but those of Mount Wu please me.
لا ترضيني أي غيوم سوى غيوم جبل وو.
Yu.
يو.
Yunlin.
يونلين.
Is that you?
هل هذا أنت؟
I know
أنا أعرف
you keep an eternal lamp in your chamber.
تحتفظ بمصباح أبدي في غرفتك.
You called me back with your longing.
اتصلت بي مجدداً وأنت تتوق إليّ.
You missed me, too?
هل اشتقت إليّ أيضاً؟
I missed you, too.
اشتقت إليك أيضاً.
What?
ماذا؟
Don't you want me?
ألا تريدني؟
Yunlin.
يونلين.
You drugged me last night?
هل دسست لي مخدراً الليلة الماضية؟
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
If we share affection,
إذا تبادلنا المودة،
why would I drug you?
لماذا سأقوم بتخديرك؟
You were so vigorous last night.
كنتَ نشيطاً جداً الليلة الماضية.
My back still aches from it.
لا يزال ظهري يؤلمني بسبب ذلك.
I hope tonight
أتمنى أن يكون هذا الليلة
you could be gentler.
بإمكانك أن تكون ألطف.
I can tolerate your usual schemes
أستطيع تحمل مكائدك المعتادة
and tricks.
والحيل.
But if you play tricks
لكن إذا لعبت الخدع
on things related to my sister,
بخصوص الأمور المتعلقة بأختي،
I won't let it slide.
لن أدع الأمر يمر مرور الكرام.
An obedient empress will stay longer
ستبقى الإمبراطورة المطيعة لفترة أطول
in her position.
في منصبها.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
do you despise me this much?
هل تحتقرني إلى هذا الحد؟
We married at a young age, after all.
لقد تزوجنا في سن مبكرة، على أي حال.
I only long for Your Majesty's affection.
لا أشتاق إلا إلى حنان جلالتكم.
Somebody.
شخص ما.
Your Majesty, you're awake.
جلالتك، أنت مستيقظ.
Let us help you dress.
دعنا نساعدك في اختيار ملابسك.
Go.
يذهب.
Bring the contraceptive decoction.
أحضري مغلي منع الحمل.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
I come from a prestigious family.
أنا أنتمي إلى عائلة مرموقة.
I'm intelligent and studious.
أنا ذكي ومجتهد.
The Grand Princess herself appointed me as empress.
لقد عينتني الأميرة الكبرى بنفسها إمبراطورة.
I've served you with
لقد خدمتكم بـ
utmost care and respect
أقصى درجات العناية والاحترام
and governed with kindness.
وحُكمت باللطف.
I have never...
لم يسبق لي...
If not for the Grand Princess,
لولا الأميرة الكبرى،
why would I make you the empress?
لماذا سأجعلك الإمبراطورة؟
Your Majesty...
جلالتكم...
My apologies, Your Majesty.
أعتذر يا صاحب الجلالة.
Will you drink this medicine yourself?
هل ستتناول هذا الدواء بنفسك؟
Or shall I...?
أم ماذا أفعل؟
I just want you to understand.
أريدك فقط أن تفهم.
Don't covet things
لا تطمع في الأشياء
that don't belong to you.
التي لا تخصك.
(Your Majesty.)
(جلالة الملك).
(You reject my love.)
(أنت ترفض حبي.)
(Then let me hate you instead.)
(إذن دعني أكرهك بدلاً من ذلك.)
(We're both pitiful souls.)
(كلانا روحان بائستان.)
(Perhaps hatred)
(ربما كراهية)
(is more fitting for this cold place.)
(هذا أنسب لهذا المكان البارد.)
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Is something wrong?
هل هناك خطب ما؟
No.
لا.
Nothing.
لا شئ.
But I bet
لكنني أراهن
you've been bored
لقد كنت تشعر بالملل
watching me work
يشاهدونني وأنا أعمل
these days.
في هذه الأيام.
I've only been reading.
لم أكن سوى أقرأ.
But Your Majesty
لكن جلالتكم
manages countless affairs and must take care of yourself.
يدير شؤوناً لا حصر لها، وعليه أن يعتني بنفسه.
With a beauty by my side,
وبجانبي حسناء،
even tedious paperwork
حتى الأعمال الورقية المملة
feels no burden.
لا يشعر بأي عبء.
Your Majesty must be busy.
لا بد أن جلالتكم مشغولة.
I shall take my leave first.
سأستأذن أولاً.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Wait in the inner chamber.
انتظر في الغرفة الداخلية.
Your Majesty, it's against the rules.
جلالة الملك، هذا مخالف للقواعد.
I made the rules.
أنا من وضع القواعد.
No one dares to comment.
لا أحد يجرؤ على التعليق.
I pay respects to Your Majesty.
أتقدم بخالص الاحترام لجلالتكم.
May Your Majesty be well.
أتمنى لجلالتكم الصحة والعافية.
Rise.
يعلو.
Quezhou's travel permits raise suspicions.
تثير تصاريح السفر الصادرة عن مدينة كويتشو الشكوك.
Tracking the gunpowder trail downward,
تتبع أثر البارود إلى الأسفل،
I found that thirty percent went to Qi State
وجدت أن ثلاثين بالمائة ذهبت إلى ولاية تشي
and the rest
والباقي
went to Hutou Mountain,
ذهبت إلى جبل هوتو،
thirty li outside the capital, through secret tunnels.
ثلاثون لي خارج العاصمة، عبر أنفاق سرية.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
I believe the mastermind
أعتقد أن العقل المدبر
likely targets the capital.
من المرجح أن يستهدف العاصمة.
If Your Majesty deploys troops to surround the mountains now,
إذا قامت جلالتكم بنشر قوات لتطويق الجبال الآن،
once the Zhuozhou case is solved,
بمجرد حل قضية تشوتشو،
we can lure the snake out of its hole.
يمكننا استدراج الثعبان للخروج من جحره.
What an excellent plan.
يا لها من خطة ممتازة.
Are you lecturing me
هل تلقي عليّ محاضرة؟
on military deployment tactics?
حول تكتيكات الانتشار العسكري؟
I dare not.
لا أجرؤ.
It's just that...
الأمر فقط هو...
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Isn't His Majesty reviewing memorials?
أليس جلالته يراجع النصب التذكارية؟
Why can't I enter?
لماذا لا أستطيع الدخول؟
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
perhaps it's best Her Majesty doesn't know I'm here.
ربما من الأفضل ألا تعلم جلالتها بوجودي هنا.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
His Majesty doesn't allow anyone in.
جلالته لا يسمح لأحد بالدخول.
Please return.
يرجى العودة.
I know
أنا أعرف
His Majesty is hiding his new favorite.
جلالته يخفي مفضله الجديد.
He's hiding that vixen inside.
إنه يخفي تلك المرأة الماكرة في الداخل.
What are they doing in there?
ماذا يفعلون هناك؟
If she covets my position,
إذا كانت تطمع في منصبي،
I'll relinquish it immediately.
سأتخلى عنه فوراً.
♪The wind rises, snow falls♪
♪تهب الرياح، ويتساقط الثلج♪
♪To stain endless remorse with red♪
♪لتلطيخ الندم الذي لا ينتهي باللون الأحمر♪
♪No regrets in moves made. Let the game unfold♪
لا ندم على الخطوات التي اتخذتها. دع اللعبة تتكشف.
♪Sorrow and joy intertwined♪
♪الحزن والفرح متشابكان♪
♪Yet we can't escape karma♪
♪لكننا لا نستطيع الهروب من الكارما♪
♪Lament this fleeting life♪
♪رثوا هذه الحياة الزائلة♪
♪So elusive♪
♪مراوغ للغاية♪
♪So indistinct♪
♪غير واضح للغاية♪
♪Resent farewells♪
♪وداعات حزينة♪
♪Remembering each other♪
♪نتذكر بعضنا البعض♪
♪Love can't be extinguished♪
♪الحب لا ينطفئ♪
♪Unwilling to accept♪
♪غير راغب في القبول♪
♪Rewriting the story♪
♪إعادة كتابة القصة♪
♪And praying♪
♪والصلاة♪
♪A long-cherished wish♪
أمنية طالما تمنيتها
♪In a daze♪
♪في حالة ذهول♪
♪Suddenly it's those years again♪
♪فجأة تعود تلك السنوات من جديد♪
♪How I wish to relive my old dreams♪
♪كم أتمنى أن أعيش أحلامي القديمة من جديد♪
♪Rewrite those torn pages♪
♪أعد كتابة تلك الصفحات الممزقة♪